https://hydraulics-pneumatics.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
Engineering HardwareHand ToolsHSS Drill BitsBall Ended Hex ScrewdriversPullers ManualTee Handle Hexagon KeysWire Loop Tee HandleMoulded Tee Handle Ball EndedMoulded Tee Handle Flat EndMoulded Tee Handle Ball EndMoulded Tee Handle 9" Flat EndedL Hexagon KeysL Keys Short Flat EndedL Keys Short Length Flat EndedL Keys Long Length Flat EndL Keys Long Length Ball EndAnti-vibrationAnti-vibration MountsMale Cylindrical BuffersMale Conical BuffersMale X Female BobbinsMale X Male BobbinsFemale Cylindrical BuffersFemale x Female BobbinsLevelling FeetFastenersCirclip Metric Internal D1300Circlip Metric External D1400Circlips Selection BoxesNutsWashersRetaining Pins BoltsSeals & GasketsRotary Shaft SealsWipersPiston SealsO RingsO Rings BS 3** 5.33mm 316" NBRO Rings BS 2** 3.53mm 18" NBRO Rings BS 1** 2.62mm 332" NBRO Rings BS 0** 1.78mm 116" NBR10-19.9mm Inside DiameterO Rings 2.4mm Cross Section0-9.9mm Inside DiameterO Ring Selection BoxesO Rings 2.0mm Cross Section50-59.9mm Inside Diameter40-49.9mm Inside DiameterO Rings 3.0mm Cross SectionO Rings 1.5mm Cross Section20-29.9mm Inside DiameterO Rings 4.0mm + Cross Section30-39.9mm Inside DiameterO Rings 2.5mm Cross SectionQuadringsU SealsCopper WashersBonded WashersFibre WashersPumps & DispensersElectricAir OperatedLiquid Jugs & DispensersGrease Nipples & GunsFurniture FittingsAdjustable FeetCaptive Nuts and InsertsPowered ToolsPullers HydraulicHydraulic Power ToolsToe JacksPressesBottle JacksPipe & TubeHose & Tube Clips & ClampsO Clip - 2 EarHose Clamp - Heavy DutyWorm Drive Clip Stainless W3Worm Drive Clip Zinc PlatedRetaining Spring ClipsTube Clamps Twin BoreFuel Line Hose ClipWorm Drive Zinc Plate Wing ScrewTube Clamps Single Bore Ext BaseTube Clamps Single BoreP Clips Rubber LinedHoses Tubing & DuctingHose ReelsSuction Delivery HosesLay- Flat Water Delivery HosePlastic & Nylon Hose for Push-InPU I/D Tube for Push-In & CompressionINCH Nylon HoseMETRIC Nylon HoseAutomotive HosesEngine Radiator HoseCar Heater HosePetrol-Fuel HoseMetal TubingStainless Steel Hydraulic TubeCarbon Steel TubeCopper Tubing AnnealedCopper Tube Half Hard StraightNominal Bore Hose for Hose TailsPVC Unreinforced Nominal BoreGas HosesAir & Compressor HosePVC Reinforced Tube Nominal boreAir & Water FittingsQuick Release Couplings19 Series (PCL)17 Series (Parker Schrader)68 Series (Parker Schrader)Twist_Air (PCL)25 Series (CEJN 320)Hose TailsEqual Elbow Hose TailsMale BSP Parallel ThreadEqual Tee Hose TailEqual Straight Hose TailMale NPT Taper ThreadFemale BSP Parallel ThreadEqual Cross 4 WayFemale Swivel Nut BSP Flat FacedMale BSP Taper ThreadJoiners 2.3 & 4 WayMale Stud Elbow Hose TailsMale BSP Taper Thread StainlessStraight Joiners StainlessReducing 3 Way WyeReducing TeeReducing StraightMale Stud Branch Tee Hose TailMale Stud Straight Hose TailsFemale Swivel Nut BSP Coned Hose TailThread AdaptorsPlugs & CapsTees Crosses & WyesCrosses and WyesTeesStraight FittingsBush BSPP Male x BSPP FemaleBush BSPP & MM x BSPP Female ExtendedNipple BSP 60 CONE ParallelBush BSPT Male x BSPP FemaleBush BSPT Male x BSPP Female ExtendedBSPP 60 CONE Parallel x TaperNipple BSP Taper x TaperFemale SocketsBulhead with LocknutNipple BSP & MM ParallelElbows & BendsPush-In Fittings for O/D TubeMale & Female Stud Push-InFemale BSP & MM ParallelMale Stud Round Body bsptMale Stud Hexagon Head bsppMale Stud BSPP/MM Push-InMale Stud Hexagon Body bsptElbow Push-InStud Elbow BSP & MM ParallelMale Stud Elbow BSP TaperStud Elbow Swivel bsptStud Elbow Swivel bsppEqual Elbow Push-InTee Wye & Cross Push-InReducing YEqual Cross Push-InEqual 3 Way WyeEqual YStraight Push-InStraight Bulkhead Push-InInch Brass BodyEqual StraightAir Brake & Automotive FittingsTee Thread AdaptorsThreaded Plugs and Sump PlugsParker Prestomatic 2 Push-InElbow Thread AdaptorsAir Brake Push-InNorgren FLEETFIT Push-InCompression FittingsMale Stud BSP TaperStraight CouplingEqual TeeFemale Stud CouplingMale Stud BSP ParallelFemale StudElbowsStem Standpipe TailBall ValvesBall Valve Brass Full Flow BSPPBall Valves Mini Brass BSPGate & Globe ValvesPumpsIndustrial Pipe FittingsClaw FittingsTrench Pump Lug FittingsBarrel Nipples bspSockets bsppStraight Joiner Connectors SteelNipples bsptEqual Tees Female bsppBend 90° Long Male x Female bspBend 90° Long Fem x Fem bspElbow 90° bspp Fem x FemElbow 90° bspt Male x bspt FemCaps bsppPlugs bsptReducing Nipples bsptReducing Bushes bspt M x bspp FBend 45° Male x Female bspBend 45° Female x Female bspReducing Sockets bspEqual Cross Female bspEqual Female Union bspMale x Female Union bspBelamBearings and BushesHydraulic PartsSeals and GasketsRubber WashersSeal RingsMechanical ComponentsElectrical & ElectronicOpto ElectronicsPlugs & ConnectorsD Connectors Sub MiniatureScrew Terminal ConnectorsDIN Square & Rectangular PlugsDIN Plugs & SocketsSwitchesMiniature Toggle SwitchesMiniature Push Button SwitchesMotorsMotorsCables & WiringCable Glands & ClampsCable GlandsElectric Wire CablesHydraulic ComponentsThread AdaptorsFemale BSPP Swivel 60 ConeSwivel Couplings BSPPThreaded Adaptors 700 BarNipples Male x MaleNipple Metric x BSPP 60° ConeBulkhead JIC UNF 37° ConedNipple Metric x Metric 60° ConeNipple BSPT x BSPTNipple BSPT x JICNipple NPT x JICBulkhead BSPP 60° ConedNipple BSPP 60° Cone x BSPTNipple NPT X BSPP 60° ConeNipple JIC x JIC UNF 37°Nipple BSPP 60° Cone x JICNipple NPT x NPTNipple BSPP x BSPP 60° ConedPlugs, Caps & NutsLocknuts for BulkheadsBSPT Hex Head PlugBSPP Solid Hex Head PlugBSPP 60 Cone Hex Head PlugORFS O Ring Face Seal Male PlugORFS O Ring Face Seal Blank CapNPT Male Solid Hex HeadJIC 37° Male Coned PlugBSPP 60 Cone Swivel Nut CapJIC 37° Female Blanking CapMETRIC Female Blanking CapMale x Swivel FemaleMale x Female Hex BodyMale BSPP X Metric Swivel FemaleMale BSPP x Female BSPPFixed Bushes & Barrel NutsMale Metric x BSPP Short Female BushExtended Bushes M x F BSPPReducing Bushes Short M x F BSPPSocket Barrel Nut BSPPTeesFemale BSPP Swivel Nut 60 Cone TeeFemale BSPP Fixed Body TeeMale BSPP 60 Cone TeeBanjo's & BoltsBanjo Bolts MetricBanjo Bolts BSPPElbows & BendsBSP Male x Female Swept BendsTube Compression FittingsStraight Male StudsBSPP Form BBSPP Form B 60 ConeBSPP Form E Adjustable StudNPT Male StudBSPP Form A 60 ConeBSPP Form EMale Stud BSPTMETRIC Form BMale Stud ElbowsTees & CrossesEqual CrossAdjustable Run TeeEqual TeesAdjustable BranchNuts, Rings, Plugs & CapsMETRIC Male PlugCompression NutsCutting Rings (Olives)ElbowsEqual ElbowsAdjustable ElbowsElbow BulkheadStraight CouplingsGauge CouplingsStraight BulkheadEqual StraightFiltersIn-Line Spin On ElementsFilter ElementsTank Top ElementsSuction StrainersSystem Pumps Valves & Power UnitsPort Flange ConnectorsPilot Operated ValvesPump Drive ConnectorsHydraulic PumpsNon Return Check ValvesLever Directional MonoblockRelief and Safety OverloadNeedle Flow Control ValvesElectric PumpsAir Hydraulic PumpsHydraulic PumpsHand PumpsValves 700 BarModular Valves CeetopHoses, Hose Ends & AssembliesHose Assemblies 700 BarFemale Nut DIN2353 24° ConeHose End Inserts, Ferrules & AccessoriesMale DIN2353 24° ConeFemale Swept 90 Bend 37° ConeFemale Straight 37° ConeMale Straight 37° ConeFemale 90° Elbow BSPP 60° ConeFemale 90° Swept Bend 60° ConeFemale 45° Swept Bend 60° ConeMale Straight BSP TaperMale Straight BSPP 60° ConeFemale Compact 90 Elbow 37° ConeFemale Swept 45 Bend 37° ConeFemale Straight BSPP 60° ConeStandpipe Swept 45° BendStandpipe StraightStandpipe 90° Swept BendFemale 90° Bend DIN2353 24° ConeBanjo Hose InsertsHose Assemblies 1 & 2 WireStraight Fem x Swept 90 FemStraight Fem x 90° FemaleStraight Fem x Straight FemStraight x Straight FemaleStraight x 90° FemaleRams - Cylinders - ActuatorsCentre Hole Double ActingCentre Hole Single ActingROUND LINE CYLINDERSShorty 10-250 TonDouble Acting 10-500 TonHigh Ton Double ActingHigh Ton Single Acting 55-565 TPancake 55-620 TonPull Single ActingAccessoriesTIE ROD CYLINDERSLow Height Single ActingGeneral Purpose S-Acting 5-100 TQuick Release CouplingsISO A PoppetFlat Face ISO 16028Hydraulic Couplers 700 BarSnap-tite H SeriesGauges Test & MeasurementGaugesGrease & OilOilsGreasesSPX Spare Parts and AccessoriesPneumaticsCylinders/ActuatorsISO 6432 CylindersISO6432 Mini Cylinders 32mm BoreISO 6432 Cylinder AccessoriesISO6432 Mini Cylinders 40mm BoreISO6432 Mini Cylinders 20mm BoreISO6432 Mini Cylinders 10mm BoreISO6432 Mini Cylinders 16mm BoreISO6432 Mini Cylinders 12mm BoreISO6432 Mini Cylinders 25mm BoreISO 6432 Mini Cylinders 8mm BoreISO 15552 CylindersISO15552 Double Act 100mm BoreISO 15552 Cylinder AccessoriesISO15552 Double Acting 32mm BoreISO15552 Double Acting 40mm BoreISO15552 Double Acting 63mm BoreISO15552 Double Acting 80mm BoreISO15552 Double Acting 50mm BoreAir Preperation FRL'sRegulatorLubricatorFilter+Regulator+LubricatorFilter RegulatorAir FilterAir/Vacuum Gauges & InstrumentationRear Centre ConnectionCentre Back Connection100mm Dry PressureDry Vacuum40mm Dry PressureBottom Stem ConnectionValvesHand Operated ValvesNon-Return ValvesFlow Control ValvesSolenoid ValvesPPE
Account
Settings
Language
Default Store View
second store view
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Please replace this text with you Privacy Policy.
Please add any additional cookies your website uses below (e.g. Google Analytics).
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that
you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this
request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Copyright © 2020 Hydraulics Pneumatics. All rights reserved.
